<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<xml><records><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>New, Joshua</author><author>Adams, Mark B.</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>Energyplus Interior Radiant Heat Exchange Runtime Performance Improvements</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>17-20</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>September 26-28, 2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>EnergyPlus is the flagship whole-building energy simulation&#xD;program developed by the US Department of Energy.&#xD;This paper describes the various approaches to improve&#xD;the performance of the interior radiant heat exchange algorithm.&#xD;Vectorization, optimized Basic Linear Algebra&#xD;Subprograms (BLAS) library, multithreading, and Graphical&#xD;Processing Unit (GPU) computation are all investigated.&#xD;The approach with the best performance, while&#xD;maintaining drop-in compatibility with existing Energy-&#xD;Plus code, is the optimized BLAS library. However, GPU&#xD;computing has the potential to reduce simulation time by&#xD;orders of magnitude with major refactoring to EnergyPlus.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16167/New_Adams_2018_Energyplus Interior Radiant Heat Exchange Runtime Performance Improvements (Paper)3.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Jha, Bandana</author><author>Bhattacharjee, Bishwajit</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>Tool for Energy Efficient Building Envelope Retrofitting</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>1-8</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>September 26-28, 2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>A major source of heat ingress in existing-buildings is through the envelopes. A bulk of cooling load in existing-buildings can be reduced by energy-efficient retrofitting of Roof, Walls and Fenestrations. The methods available for calculating heat ingress in largescale existing structures are lengthy/cumbersome and manually impractical. The popular energy simulation software is black-box type requiring specialized technical skills, voluminous data-entries, several iterations and does not automatically select the most energy-efficient envelope retrofitting material out of available options in the local market. This paper proposes a user-friendly spread-sheet based model of a tool for automatically selecting energy-efficient envelope retrofit solutions from the available options.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16165/Jha_Bhattacharjee_2018_Tool for Energy Efficient Building Envelope Retrofitting (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Rao, Sagar</author><author>Conant-Gilles, David</author><author>Jia, Yiyuan</author><author>Carl, Brittany</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>Rapid Modeling of Large and Complex High Performance Buildings Using Energyplus</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>9-16</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>September 26-28, 2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>EnergyPlus has long been relegated to a niche within the professional building performance modeling world due to a steep learning curve and the time needed to deliver complex models. However, advancement of energy codes, high performance design, and net zero energy aspirations have increased simulation complexity and the desire for accuracy. Achieving these goals requires design teams to quickly evaluate complex building systems, yet maintain flexibility to revise models as the design progresses. Designing high performance buildings requires assessment of numerous strategies including advanced envelopes, complex airflow arrangements, high-efficiency hydronic systems, custom control sequences, and the like. DOE’s EnergyPlus simulation engine is a natural choice as it is flexible, programmable, includes sophisticated heat transfer models, enables component controls, etc.&#xD;&#xD;This paper demonstrates how state-of-the-art computing techniques can be used to create modular EnergyPlus models for cloud-powered rapid simulation and visualization. The authors introduce this modeling platform and describe the process automation achieved, resulting in input uniformity while maintaining zones, systems and plant customization. The authors also present results for tests carried out to evaluate the scalability and robustness of these models to demonstrate the viability of incorporating EnergyPlus in standard modeling workflows for rapid consulting. This process allows teams to leverage EnergyPlus to more accurately model building physics while reducing model assembly time. Simulation runtime reduction is also discussed. Results are presented for two buildings – i) a 385,000 sf laboratory and office facility with ZNE goals; and ii) a 780,000 sf mixed use campus with rapid design-assist modeling needs.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16166/Rao et al_2018_Rapid Modeling of Large and Complex High Performance Buildings Using Energyplus (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Rakha, Tarek</author><author>Chen, Yuanyue</author><author>Reinhart, Christoph</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>Do Office Buildings ‘Save’ Energy in the United States Due to Daylight Saving Time (dst)? A 50-State Simulation-Based Study</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>21-28</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>This paper investigates the “savings” in Daylight Saving Time (DST) through a comprehensive simulation-based study. A United States Department of Energy (US DOE) core and perimeter reference small office building was simulated with and without DST for each state across the seven US climate zones using benchmark inputs. The “lightswitch” model was used to represent probabilistically-valid user behavior for lighting energy, using DIVA for Grasshopper as the front-end for Radiance and Daysim, and resulting schedules were used as input for the EnergyPlus thermal zone models, using Archsim for Grasshopper. Results demonstrate a range up to 7% lighting energy savings when DST is not applied in 36 states. On average, the application of DST did not save energy in simulated small office spaces across the country, and caused an increase of 0.1% in total energy consumption. The paper concludes by discussing the validity of continuing to apply DST in the US.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16168/Rakha et al_2018_Do Office Buildings ‘Save’ Energy in the United States Due to Daylight Saving (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Rentfro, Sarah</author><author>Nicastro, Anthony</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>State of the Industry – Computer-Aided Simulation of High-Performance Building Enclosures</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>29-36</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>Computer-aided simulations are commonly used to predict building enclosure performance. Without informed guidance, however, they may produce inaccurate or misleading results that lead to performance failures. This paper explores common shortcomings and challenges associated with simulation of building enclosure assemblies through review of a broad range of software and simulation scenarios. Topics discussed include quantitative and qualitative simulation constraints, reliability of inputs, significance and integration of project-specific data, and interpretation of results.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16169/Rentfro_Nicastro_2018_State of the Industry – Computer-Aided Simulation of High-Performance Building (Paper).pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Hao, Zhengwen</author><author>O’Neill, Zheng</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>Model-Based Estimation of Building Infiltration</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>37-44</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>Building infiltration measurement is a challenge. To address current challenge, a scalable and low cost Building Infiltration Estimator with Ultrasonic Thermometry (BLAST) is proposed. The proposed method contains the physical measurements and a model-based estimation. This paper is focusing on the model-based estimation part, which uses an Extended Kalman filter (EKF) to inversely estimate the building infiltration using measurements of surface temperature and total heat flux, and a low-order state-space model. An EnergyPlus-based emulator is used to generate a virtual building and measurements to test the proposed estimation method. Nearly 80% estimated infiltration resistances are within the 20% error band compared to the calculated infiltration resistance from EnergyPlus. This preliminary study shows the EKF based estimator with the proposed measurements is promising for building infiltration estimation.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16170/Hao_O’Neill_2018_Model-Based Estimation of Building Infiltration (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Liu, Bing</author><author>Rosenberg, Michael</author><author>Athalye, Rahul</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>National Impact of ANSI/ASHRAE/IES Standard 90.1-2016</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>45-52</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>ANSI/ASHRAE/IES Standard 90.1 is the U.S. national commercial building model energy code and it has a significant impact on many programs and policies that impact energy savings across the United States and the world. Determining the energy savings from the latest edition of Standard 90.1 relative to previous editions is critical for beyond code programs and for others setting energy performance targets. Pacific Northwest National Laboratory developed prototype building models to determine the energy savings from 90.1-2016 standard. This paper presents the rigorous modeling and development process that PNNL has established and its applications. In addition, the energy savings results of Standard 90.1-2016 are described.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16171/Liu et al_2018_National Impact of ANSI-ASHRAE-IES Standard 90 (Paper)3.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Baker, Chris</author><author>Goel, Supriya</author><author>Wang, Nora</author><author>Rosenberg, Michael</author><author>Wolf, Doug</author><author>Henderson, Paul</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>A Simplified Energy Modeling Approach for Buildings</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>54-59</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>This paper introduces simplified energy modeling (SEM) approaches using DOE2 and EnergyPlus and proposes a validation method for simplified energy modeling. Simplified energy modeling can allow more design teams and owners to leverage the power of energy modeling to inform their designs and lead to greater energy savings and a lower first cost because the technologies and design strategies can be thoroughly tested against models before the decisions are made. By starting a discussion on how to develop simplified energy modeling approaches and methods to validate results, we hope to increase innovation in energy modeling software while decreasing variation between modelers.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16172/Baker et al_2018_A Simplified Energy Modeling Approach for Buildings (Paper).pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Ali, Usman</author><author>Shamsi, Mohammad Haris</author><author>Alshehri, Fawaz</author><author>Mangina, Eleni</author><author>O'Donnel, James</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>Comparative Analysis of Machine Learning Algorithms for Building Archetypes Development in Urban Energy Modeling</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>60-67</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>The most common approach for urbn building energy modeling (UBEM) involves segmenting a building stock into archetypes.  Development Building archetypes for urban scale is a complex task and requires a lot of extensive data. The archietype development methodology proposed in this paper uses unsupervised machine learning approaches to identify similar clusters of buildings based on specific features. The archetype development process considers four crucial processes of machine learning: data preprocessing, feature selection, clustering algorithm adaptation and results validation. The four different clustering algorithms investigated in this study are K-Mean, Hierarchical, Density-based, K-Medoids.  All the algorithms are applied on Irish Energy Performance Certificate (EPS) that consist of 203 features. The obtained results are then used to compare and analyze the chosen algorithms with respect to performance, quality and cluster instances. The K-mean algorithm performs best in terms of cluster formation.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16173/Ali et al_2018_Comparative Analysis of Machine Learning Algorithms for Building Archetypes (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Kontar, Rawad El</author><author>Rakha, Tarek</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>Profiling Occupancy Patterns in Community-Scale Residential Buildings Using Measured Energy Use Data Clustering</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>68-75</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>Uncertainty in predicting occupancy patterns leads to discrepancies in simulated building energy compared to measured data. Typical simulation models represent occupants through identical schedules and repetitive behavior. However, users’ activity patterns comprise numerous variations, especially when focusing on occupants’ interactions on neighborhood scale. This paper presents a framework for modeling occupancy and consequent energy loads in residential buildings using measured data for calibration; it employs a clustering approach to profile energy use which generates inputs for Urban Energy Models (UBEMs). The framework is demonstrated on a residential neighborhood and reveals that the generated inputs can more accurately predict energy load patterns.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16174/Kontar_Rakha_2018_Profiling Occupancy Patterns in Community-Scale Residential Buildings Using (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Jaeger, Ina De</author><author>Ma, Yixiao</author><author>Saelens, Dirk</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>Estimating Window Dimensions of Residential Buildings in District Energy Models</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>76-83</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>This work focuses on the impact of the window-to-wall ratio (WWR) on the energy demand for space heating and the building overheating through the evaluation of three WWR acquisition methods and four WWR allocation levels for a virtual district, containing 174 single-family dwellings. A new WWR acquisition method, based on a database, is proposed and evaluated. The impact of the WWR on the energy demand for space heating is limited (root mean square percentage errors up to 0.07), whereas the impact on the overheating is significantly higher (root mean square percentage errors up to 12.4). Both errors are higher for newer buildings compared to older buildings.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16175/Jaeger et al_2018_Estimating Window Dimensions of Residential Buildings in District Energy Models (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Ali, Usman</author><author>Shamsi, Mohammad Haris</author><author>Hoare, Cathal</author><author>Mangina, Eleni</author><author>O’Donnell, James</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>An Intelligent Knowledge-Based Energy Retrofit Recommendation System for Residential Buildings at an Urban Scale</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>84-91</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>Buildings play a significant role in driving the urban demand and supply of energy. Research conducted in the urban buildings sector indicates that there is a considerable potential to achieve significant reductions in energy consumption and greenhouse gas emissions. These reductions are possible through retrofitting existing buildings into more efficient and sustainable buildings. Building retrofitting poses a huge challenge for owners and city planners because they usually lack expertise and resources to identify and evaluate cost-effective energy retrofit strategies. This paper proposes a new methodology based on machine learning algorithms to develop an intelligent knowledge-based recommendation system which has the ability to recommend energy retrofit measures. The proposed methodology is based on the following four steps: archetypes development, knowledge-base development, recommendation system development and building retrofitting or performance analysis. A case study of Irish buildings dataset shows that the proposed system can provide effective energy retrofits recommendation and improve building energy performance.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16176/Ali et al_2018_An Intelligent Knowledge-Based Energy Retrofit Recommendation System for (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Han, Jung Min</author><author>Reinhart, Christoph</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>Development of the Urban Surface Management Software for Pvs and Stormwater with Connectivity to Urban Modeling Interface</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild2018</full-title></periodical><pages>92-99</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>As green technologies are becoming more frequently integrated into the architectural design, there is a growing need for tools to support architects conducting environmental analyses. Especially in urban-scale analyses, green technologies such as photovoltaics (PVs) and green roofs have led to significant electricity production and reduction in carbon emissions. PVs have developed from applications of different scales, and now are a major source of electricity. Another way of managing urban areas is Low Impact Development (LID). Especially important is the potential of horizontal surfaces in urban areas, which comprise the largest portion of surfaces useful to green technology. For example, roofs represent up to 32% of the horizontal surfaces in built-up areas (Frazer, 2005), and thus are related to potential energy fluctuations and water management. In practice, it is currently quite difficult to simulate or predict the benefits and overall effects of deploying PVs because most urban-scale modeling tools provide only limited functionality when applied to green technology. This research has developed urban analysis add-ons for Rhinoceros and Grasshopper that address green technology such as PVs and LID and investigated their potential benefits. By including a case study of proposed tools with connectivity to umi (Reinhart, 2013), this research offers an important urban-scale implementation of green technology.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16177/Han_Reinhart_2018_Development of the Urban Surface Management Software for Pvs and Stormwater (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Hong, Tianzhen</author><author>Luo, Xuan</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>Modeling Building Energy Performance in Urban Context</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>100-106</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>Many buildings already exist in an urban context, in close proximity to many other buildings of similar or larger size and in micro-climates (e.g., urban canyons and heat islands) created by this environment. As the world’s population increasingly flows into cities, many more buildings will fit this description.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16178/Hong_Luo_2018_Modeling Building Energy Performance in Urban Context (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Khanie, Mandana Sarey</author><author>Kj, Susanne V.</author><author>Wienold, Jan</author><author>Andersen, Maryline</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>A Gaze Visualizer Tool Implementation of Gaze Data into Lighting Rendering Tools Using Radiance and Honeybee for Grasshopper3d</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>107-112</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>The Gaze Visualizer tool is an implementation of eyetracking (gaze) data and a preliminary gaze responsive light driven (GRL) model, which enables to visualize gaze behavior in a 3D space, in Grasshopper3D. The workflow from obtaining the relevant photometric quantities, retrieving gaze data, intorduction of the GRL model to the tool and a simple data representation scheme are presented here. The final plugin is easy to use for Rhino/Grasshopper developers with only basic skills, and provides a quick estimations of the gaze respionsive visual comfort in an illustrative way, that gives the user an adequate overview of the glare-free zones in the room.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16179/Khanie et al_2018_A Gaze Visualizer Tool Implementation of Gaze Data into Lighting Rendering (Paper).pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Gracik, Stefan</author><author>Landsman, Jared</author><author>Sit, Ryan</author><author>Takahashi, Ken</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>Changing California Code: Finding the Next Savings Opportunities</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>114-118</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>Every three years, the Codes and Standards Enhancement (CASE) Initiative recommends updates to the California Building Energy Efficiency Standards (Title 24, Part 6). This paper documents the feasibility, energy implications, and cost implications of four proposed code changes for the 2019 code cycle: ASHARE 62.1 alignment, ASHRAE 90.1 alignment, cooling tower minimum efficiency updates, and new lab exhaust regulations. The assessment considers an examination of the state of the market, energy savings, life-cycle costs, and statewide consequences. Finally, the paper discusses modeling challenges that arise when trying to predict savings at a large scale and its implications on code.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16180/Gracik et al_2018_Changing California Code (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Liu, Yue</author><author>Colburn, Alex</author><author>Inanici, Mehlika</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>Computing Long-Term Daylighting Simulations from High Dynamic Range Imagery Using Deep Neural Networks</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>119-126</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>Compared with illuminance-based metrics, luminancebased metrics and evaluations provide better understandings of occupant visual experience. However, it is computationally expensive and time consuming to incorporate luminance-based metrics into architectural design practice because annual simulations require generating a luminance map at each time step of the entire year. This paper describes the development of a novel prediction model to generate annual luminance maps of indoor space from a subset of images by using deep neural networks (DNNs). The results show that by only rendering 5% of annual luminance maps, the proposed DNNs model can predict the rest with comparable accuracy that closely matches those highquality point-in-time renderings generated by Radiance (RPICT) software. This model can be applied to accelerate annual luminance-based simulations and lays the groundwork for generating annual luminance maps utilizing High Dynamic Range (HDR) captures of existing environments.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16181/Liu et al_2018_Computing Long-Term Daylighting Simulations from High Dynamic Range Imagery (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Celik, Kemal</author><author>Mead, Alex R.</author><author>Mosalam, Khalid</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>Hybrid Simulation for Daylighting of Complex Fenestration Systems for Building Envelopes</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>127-131</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>This paper reports the status of new hybrid simulation for daylight analysis method under development. The method combines both full-scale physical measurements and computational techniques, providing analysis results of complex fenestration system (CFS) with increased realism while keeping costs in check and, for the first time, the repeatability of excitation conditions at fullscale. The simulation method divides the physics of daylighting into the two primary components: direct and diffuse light. Preliminary results of the diffuse component of the system and the current state of the heliodon is presented in the paper for a novel CFS known as translucent concrete panels for energy-efficient building envelopes.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16182/Celik et al_2018_Hybrid Simulation for Daylighting of Complex Fenestration Systems for Building (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Hamidpour, Maryam</author><author>Blouin, Vincent</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>Development of a Comparison-Based Control Strategy of Electrochromic Glazing for the Management of Indoor Lighting and Energy Efficiency</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>133-140</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>The daylight performance of buildings can be controlled by using electrochromic (EC) glazing as the tint of the EC glass can be altered by the application of an electrical voltage. One issue, however, is the selection of the strategy to control the tint level and obtain appropriate daylight and the least energy consumption. A new control strategy is proposed, which consists of comparing the simulated performances of all possible EC states and selecting the most appropriate at all times. The new strategy is compared to two commonly used strategies to show its ability to improve both lighting performance and energy efficiency.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16183/Hamidpour_Blouin_2018_Development of a Comparison-Based Control Strategy of Electrochromic Glazing (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Dutta, Ranojoy</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>Modeling an Electrochromic Window Using a Multi-Criteria Control Strategy</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>149-156</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>Electrochromic (EC) glazing products have the ability to actively control solar transmission based on low voltage input. While this technology has been around for several years, the default options to model EC glazing in current simulation tools is still limited and often does not allow a full evaluation of multi-state EC products with predictive controls. Given a growing interest from the design community for incorporating EC glazing in high performance and net zero energy buildings, this paper will present a methodology for modeling a commercially available multi-state EC product with the actual control logic using EMS and compare the results with the default modeling approach.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16184/Dutta_2018_Modeling an Electrochromic Window Using a Multi-Criteria Control Strategy (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Arendt, K.</author><author>Jradi, M.</author><author>Shaker, H. R.</author><author>Veje, C. T.</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>Comparative Analysis of White-, Gray- and Black-Box Models for Thermal Simulation of Indoor Environment: Teaching Building Case Study</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>173-180</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>This study presents a performance comparison between selected white-, gray- and black-box models for indoor temperature prediction in a university building located at the SDU Campus Odense. It was found that the blackbox models outperform the gray- and white-box models in most cases, but the accuracy highly depends on the training data in terms of both period and modes of heat transfer covered by the data set. The average mean absolute error for the best performing black-box model was 0.4ƕC as compared to 1.0ƕC and 0.7ƕC for the gray-box and whitebox models, respectively. In terms of accuracy, the graybox models are a reasonable alternative for black-box only in case of short-term predictions, in which their error decreases to around 0.3-0.8ƕC , depending on the room.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16185/Arendt et al_2018_Comparative Analysis of White-, Gray- and Black-Box Models for Thermal (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Zani, Andrea</author><author>Mainini, Andrea G.</author><author>Cadena, Juan D. Blanco</author><author>Schiavon, Stefano</author><author>Arens, Edward</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>A New Modeling Approach for the Assessment of the Effect of Solar Radiation on Indoor Thermal Comfort</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>181-188</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>Thermal-comfort modeling has traditionally incorporated radiant effects via the metrics mean radiant temperature (MRT) and radiant temperature asymmetry. These metrics have not until recently, considered the effect of incoming solar radiation directly heating the occupants, though it significantly affects their thermal comfort.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16186/Zani et al_2018_A New Modeling Approach for the Assessment of the Effect of Solar Radiation on (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Pandey, Brijesh</author><author>Sharma, Atul</author><author>Banerjee, Rangan</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>Prediction of Improved Occupant's Thermal Comfort with Ceiling Fan Through Coupled Energy Simulation and Computational Fluid Dynamics</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>189-196</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>Ceiling fans are considered as effective energy saving option for occupant’s thermal comfort improvement. In this study, a generic method is developed to integrate the effect of air flow induced by a ceiling fan in a whole building simulation model to quantify its effect on occupant’s thermal comfort and associated reduced cooling energy demand. A co-simulation between EnergyPlus and Computational Fluid Dynamics (CFD) has been performed. A generalized interface is developed using Matlab and Building Control Virtual Test Bed (BCVTB) to couple EnergyPlus and Fluent for co-simulation. A cubical room comprising a window having dimensions of 3m×3m×3m and 2m×2m respectively and equipped with a ceiling fan is taken to illustrate the applicability of the method. Simulation is performed for the typical summer day of Mumbai city of India. This paper concludes that for considered case using ceiling fan improves thermal comfort index by 38% and reduces cooling load by 27%.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16187/Pandey et al_2018_Prediction of Improved Occupant's Thermal Comfort with Ceiling Fan Through (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Anand, Y.</author><author>Verma, S. K.</author><author>Anand, S.</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>Transient 3-D Modelling of Ceiling Fan for Achieving Thermal Comfort</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild2018</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>197-204</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>In this study, our aim is to check, compare and validate the 3-dimensional transient model of a ceiling fan using Computational Fluid Dynamics. This is done by comparing the experimentally measured values with simulated values of air velocities at various precisely located points, in a building envelope, for achieving thermal comfort, using ceiling fan by ANSYS 18.2. As, the flow of air originating from fan is having turbulent nature and there are so many models available, so choosing the correct model is necessity. In this study, the comparison of the experimental work is done for the four most widely used turbulence models i.e. the standard k- ω, the SST k-ω, the standard k-ε and the Realizable k-ε. After the analysis and comparison it was found that the result obtained from the SST k-ω are best suited to model for this type of problem, as the simulated values thus obtained shows agreement of 94% with the experimented values.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16188/Anand et al_2018_Transient 3-D Modelling of Ceiling Fan for Achieving Thermal Comfort (Paper).pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Kohoutková, Alžběta</author><author>Horváthová, Jana</author><author>Kny, Martin</author><author>Nehasil, Ondřej</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>Case Study of Occupant’s Perception of Indoor Thermal Conditions Under Different Heating Systems</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>205-212</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>This study is focused on a human perception of a thermal environment. The human perception is influenced by many factors, for example activity, clothing, age, gender and psychological condition. In the laboratory thermal conditions of outdoor and indoor environment were artificially simulated. Experiments were repetitively held on the group of 24 occupants for different kinds of heating systems. These occupants were of same age and wore same kind of clothing. Half of them were male and half female. The aim of the sets of experiments was to assess a of occupants´ perception of the thermal conditions.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16189/Kohoutková et al_2018_Case Study of Occupant’s Perception of Indoor Thermal Conditions Under (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Tarkhan, Nada</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>The Development of an Indoor Environmental Monitoring Framework for Post-Occupancy Evaluation Using Real-Time Web-Tools</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>213-220</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>The Arup Boston Office has recently relocated to a new space in which it has reinforced workplace wellness and has been awarded both WELL and Fitwel certifications. In order to evaluate the impact of wellness strategies implemented, a Post-Occupancy Evaluation (POE) was conducted that utilized an in-house designed sensor kit that records environmental parameters including dry bulb temperature (C), relative humidity (%), horizontal illumination level (lux), carbon dioxide (CO2) concentration (ppm), particulate matter (PM 1, 2.5,10) and VOCs (Volatile Organic Compounds).</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16190/Tarkhan_2018_The Development of an Indoor Environmental Monitoring Framework for (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Williamson, Jennifer L.</author><author>Hu, Chen</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>Glazing in Commercial Buildings - the Balance Between Cost and Energy Consumption</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>221-228</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>This paper explores the balance between reducing energy use and intial costs over the life cycle of glazing options. More specifically, this paper discusses the results of parametric analysis on a calibrated building energy model of a single-story office building with multiple glazing options, including: double or triple glazed insulated glazing units (IGU), low-emissivity (low-e) coatings, window-to-wall ratios (WWR), and gas fillers. The model was used to predict energy consumption; Skanska performed detailed cost estimates to provide upfront costs; and the model’s results were combined with typical energy costs to estimate longterm costs.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16191/Williamson_Hu_2018_Glazing in Commercial Buildings - the Balance Between Cost and Energy (Paper).pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Delzendeh, Elham</author><author>Wu, Song</author><author>Alaaeddine, Rima</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>The Role of Space Design in Prediction of Occupancy in Multi- Functional Spaces of Public Buildings</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>229-236</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>In building energy predictions, the default occupancy is defined by the space function with fixed schedules. However, the occupancy of public buildings, such as galleries, recreational and educational buildings, have great variations during high and low seasons. In multifunctional public spaces, occupancy is related to space design features, which would determine the types of activities and occupants’ duration of presences. This research investigates the impacts of space design on occupancy in multifunctional spaces of public buildings using multiple cases. This study confirms that considering actual space design features will contribute in improving the accuracy of energy predictions in public buildings.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16192/Delzendeh et al_2018_The Role of Space Design in Prediction of Occupancy in Multi- Functional Spaces (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Hemsath, Timothy</author><author>Yow, Joel</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>Exploring Geometric Sensitivity Using Rapid Energy Performance Simulation</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>237-241</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>With increasing code expectations on lighting, mechanical and electrical systems more pressure is placed on the architectural design of buildings. However, little is known about the geometric sensitivity of the architectural form related to energy performance. Various studies highlight the reciprocal relationship between certain building types and specific climates. The studies are limited in that they explore single building use types, single climates, and simple building geometry. This paper will describe a custom tool titled Rapid Energy Performance Simulator (REPS) allowing design teams to explore in any climate the energy performance of extruded footprints, building orientation, window wall ratio, and aids in prioritizing shading. The REPS tool is designed to work with few initial inputs, novice software users, and early conceptual design. Analysis of resulting geometric results across climate zones provides insight into the geometric sensitivity of the building’s shape on energy efficiency and validates the value of REPS for early building performance simulation of energy use.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16193/Hemsath_Yow_2018_Exploring Geometric Sensitivity Using Rapid Energy Performance Simulation (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Brandan, Maria Alejandra Menchaca</author><author>Espinosa, FA Dominguez</author><author>Tomasetti, Thornton</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>Modeling Natural Ventilation in Early and Late Design Stages: Developing the Right Simulation Workflow with the Right Inputs</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>243-249</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>Designing natural ventilation systems involves different levels of sophistication in calculations and software tools according to the system complexity and the stage of the design process. This paper provides a general workflow to model these systems, while describing the types of resources available for different complexities and design stages. Inputs needed at each step of the workflow are discussed, and, when not available anywhere else, ways to compute them are also presented. Particularly, this paper shows how to account for the ventilation efficiency of various window types and pressure losses of obstructions along the airflow path when their discharge coefficient is unknown.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16194/Brandan et al_2018_Modeling Natural Ventilation in Early and Late Design Stages (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Lu, Xing</author><author>Fu, Yangyang</author><author>Zuo, Wangda</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>Modeling of Connected Community Infrastructures Accounting for the Interdependencies Among Energy, Transportation, and Communication Networks</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>250-257</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>A future connected community is rendered as an aggregate of sophisticated public infrastructure not only the energy system but also the transportation and communication networks, intertwined with each other. The issues multiply when researchers start juggling how, when, and where to allocate heterogeneous infrastructures, such as renewable energy sources, electric vehicles, and advanced wireless communication and sensor systems. In order to achieve a globally optimum operation and cost reductions, energy, transportation and communication networks should be modeled and optimized collectively. In this paper, a preliminary connected community package implemented in Modelica is proposed considering the interdependency between these three networks. In this package, a connected community is divided into multiple regional blocks. Each block has three system agents including an agent for energy consumption and renewable generation, an agent for transportation which includes an electric vehicle station, and an agent for communication. The three different system agents in energy, transportation, and communication are interconnected through different interfaces. For the energy system agent, the cable model links the interaction of different energy agents. For the transportation system agent, the road model is built to simulate the commuting between the different blocks. For the communication system agent, the transmission model is built to mimic reduction or delay in transmitting the information flow. Finally, a case study is presented to demonstrate how the transportation and communication networks influence on the operation of the energy systems between various blocks.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16195/Lu et al_2018_Modeling of Connected Community Infrastructures Accounting for the (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Ruya, Elvin</author><author>Augenbroe, Godfried</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>Exploring Thermal Comfort Acceptance Criteria in Energy Modeling</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>258-265</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>Thermal comfort dominates the decisions on the HVAC (heating, ventilation, air conditioning) sizing and operations. Despite industry standards aim to achieve the perfect occupant comfort, they mostly fail in occupant satisfaction and cause superfluous energy consumption. Similar to design practices, energy modeling tools also depend on the predefined standards to determine the acceptable thermal comfort levels which leads to system oversizing.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16196/Ruya_Augenbroe_2018_Exploring Thermal Comfort Acceptance Criteria in Energy Modeling (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Hamedani, Zahra</author><author>Solgi, Ebrahim</author><author>Skates, Henry</author><author>Khanie, Mandana Sarey</author><author>Fernando, Ruwan</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>A Calibration and Adjustment Method for a Dynamic Visual Comfort Assessment</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>266-273</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>Glare is known as one of the main causes of visual discomfort in office space and yet remains difficult to evaluate quantitatively. Most discomfort glare models have limitations when attempting to represent the reality of user behaviour. One reason is that models are developed based only on subjective surveys. This research aims to probe the influence of experiencing glare on user ocular and dynamic gaze behaviour as an objective response. To do so, an experimental study was conducted utilizing an eye-tracking device to record user’s gaze responses to the surrounding environment. High dynamic range imaging was also used to record luminance distribution. This paper documents the calibration process for the variety of equipment utilized in this research.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16197/Hamedani et al_2018_A Calibration and Adjustment Method for a Dynamic Visual Comfort Assessment (Paper).pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Jones, Nathaniel L.</author><author>Goehring, Alexej</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>Aeroacoustic Façade Noise: Predicting Wind-Induced Noise from Perforated Façade Panels</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>274-281</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>In this paper, we propose a method to quantify the likelihood that perforated exterior façade panels will produce wind-induced noise. This noise is generated by pressure fluctuations when vortices shed off the panels. The frequency and audibility are influenced by panel geometry, wind velocity, turbulence, and wind angle of incidence. We performed parametric computational fluid dynamic (CFD) analyses of perforated panels to calculate sound pressure levels and trained a machine learning algorithm on that data. We applied the learned relationship to a building scale CFD analysis accounting for annual variation of wind direction and strength to predict the likelihood of noise at any location on the building for a typical weather year.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16198/Jones_Goehring_2018_Aeroacoustic Façade Noise (Paper).pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Traube, Caroline Fluhrer</author><author>Spies, Skander</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>Considerations for the Design and Energy Modeling of New Commercial Buildings with Increased Ventilation Rates</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>282-289</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>The 30% more ventilation than ASHRAE 62.1 design criterion has been a long-considered option for design teams pursuing LEED certification to attempt improved indoor air quality for occupants. Emerging research is now discussing the potential cognitive benefits of increasing ventilation rates even further above code minimum levels. This paper outlines key design and modeling questions for practitioners to consider when asked to evaluate the impacts of increased ventilation targets. This paper explores setting performance goals, expected indoor carbon dioxide (CO2) values, occupancy patterns, energy use, and system sizing implications. A case study example building in Seattle is used to provide building simulation examples and insights.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16199/Traube_Spies_2018_Considerations for the Design and Energy Modeling of New Commercial Buildings (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Baffa, Matthew David</author><author>Wach, David Raymond</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>Assessing Indoor Concentrations of Formaldehyde in Single- Detached Canadian Households Due to Oriented Strand Board (osb) Wall Sheathing</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>290-297</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>Oriented strand board (OSB) is a building material used in new Canadian residential household construction. OSB emits formaldehyde, a suspected carcinogen that may pose a health risk to residents of Canadian households. This study employs a time-averaged mass balance model and Monte Carlo simulations under quasi-steady state conditions to assess indoor concentrations of formaldehyde attributed to the presence of OSB wall sheathing within the building envelope of single-detached Canadian households. This study suggests 7.6% to 14% of the total indoor concentration of formaldehyde could be attributed to the off gassing of OSB wall sheathing during initial homeowner occupancy.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16200/Baffa_Wach_2018_Assessing Indoor Concentrations of Formaldehyde in Single- Detached Canadian (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Vázquez-Canteli, José</author><author>Ulyanin, Stepan</author><author>Kämpf, Jérôme</author><author>Nagy, Zoltán</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>Adaptive Multi-Agent Control of Hvac Systems for Residential Demand Response Using Batch Reinforcement Learning</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>683-690</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>Demand response allows consumers to reduce their electrical consumption during periods of peak energy use. This reduces the peaks of electrical demand, and, consequently, the wholesale electricity prices. However, buildings must coordinate with each other to avoid delaying their electricity consumption simultaneously, which would create new, delayed peaks of electrical demand. In this work, we examine this coordination using batch reinforcement learning (BRL). BRL does not require a model, and allows the buildings to adapt over time to the optimal behavior. We implemented our controller in CitySim, a building simulator, using TensorFlow, a machine learning library.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16251/Vázquez-Canteli et al_2018_Adaptive Multi-Agent Control of Hvac Systems for Residential Demand Response (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Kim, Hye Gi</author><author>Sung, Jae Eun</author><author>Kim, Sun Sook</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>Analaysis of a Large-Scale Database for Energy Performance Modeling of Existing Buildings</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>691-698</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>As the importance of energy efficiency improvement and management of existing buildings increases, the importance of energy simulation and energy use evaluation of existing buildings is also increasing. However, unlike new building, the level of available information that can be entered into the simulation varies from building to building. Therefore, in various countries were developing and providing a reference model of the existing buildings for evaluating energy performance by using the available information or the standards according to completion year of the building. However, information that can not be gathered is usually input assumed value by the case study or previous studies. The ultimate goal of this study is to replace the assumed values of variables with more accurate and reliable information by calibrating the model output with measurement data. And, it is to provide which not a single reference building but a reference building pakage that can be evaluated to reflect various building characteristics across the country. This study is a basic study for this purpose, to develop a reference building pakage for the national-wide offices according to the existing reference building development method and to present the calibration direction by comparing it with the available information of the existing building.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16252/Kim et al_2018_Analaysis of a Large-Scale Database for Energy Performance Modeling of Existing (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Firth, Steven</author><author>Kole, Gareth</author><author>Kane, Tom</author><author>Hassan, Tarek</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>An Open Science Approach for Building Performance Studies</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>699-706</pages><keywords><keyword>120202 Building Science and Techniques</keyword></keywords><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><electronic-resource-num>10.17028/RD.LBORO.2070091.V1</electronic-resource-num><abstract>Open Science is increasingly viewed as a priority for collaboration and advancement of scientific disciplines. This paper presents two Open Science methods for building performance studies: i) a method for storing building performance information using an open data format, including the creation of a custom XML schema and the novel use of both XML and CSV formats for data storage; and ii) a method for carrying out building performance analysis in an open and reproducible manner using the Jupyter Notebook tool.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>DOI.org (Datacite)</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><web-urls><url>https://repository.lboro.ac.uk/articles/REFIT_Smart_Home_dataset/2070091/1</url></web-urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16253/Firth et al_2018_An Open Science Approach for Building Performance Studies (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><access-date>2020-04-15 01:38:49</access-date><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Nikkho, Saber Khoshdel</author><author>Steffensen, Jeff</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>Reduced-Order Energy Modeling in Retro-Commissioning: A Case Study of an Academic Building</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>707-712</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>This case study investigates the potential energy savings in retro-commissioning an existing building on the University of Virginia’s campus using a reduced-order energy model. The retro-commissioning is focused on HVAC operation, including ventilation reduction and air terminal unit operation. The potential energy savings from the retro-commissioning’s recommended measures are evaluated in a building reduced-order energy model. Prior to the evaluation, the energy model is iteratively calibrated using the building utilities data based on ASHRAE Guideline 14 to ensure accuracy. Based on the reduced-order energy model, the recommended measures result in more than 11% savings in energy cost annually.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16254/Nikkho_Steffensen_2018_Reduced-Order Energy Modeling in Retro-Commissioning (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Chang, Roger</author><author>Crawley, Drury B.</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>Influence of Plug and Process Loads and Occupancy on Ultimate Energy Savings – a New Approach</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>713-720</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>The energy utilization index (EUI) is commonly used to describe a building's energy performance. But this index has significant shortcomings because it does not address space utilization, occupant density, plug or process loads. This paper explores a bottom-up approach for energy benchmarking, both for design optimization and portfolio analysis, utilizing a concept known as energy usage effectiveness (EUE). EUE is the ratio of a building's total energy use divided by an adapted calculation of unregulated process energy use. We started by evaluating benchmark EUE values using all 16 DOE Commercial Prototype Buildings for ASHRAE Standard 90.1-2013 for the full range of ASHRAE climate zones. In this paper, we compare EUE to calculated EUI to highlight correlations and divergences. We explore normalized and non-normalized approaches to treatment of unregulated process loads and the impact of significant variation in these loads on EUE. This includes the impact of occupant density and corresponding ventilation rates. We also compare how these results relate to the Standard 90.1 building performance factor methodology. As outcome-based energy code compliance pathways are introduced, there is a need for target setting for code compliance and stretch energy codes that ultimately scale to building utilization, rather than fixed values most commonly tied to the 2003 and 2012 Commercial Buildings Energy Consumption Survey.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16255/Chang_Crawley_2018_Influence of Plug and Process Loads and Occupancy on Ultimate Energy Savings – (Paper).pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Zhang, Yuna</author><author>Augenbroe, Godfried</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>Optimal Strategy for Demand Charge Reduction in an Office Building Under Different Rate Structure</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>721-728</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>This paper targets the optimal combination of design and operational measures in a new design or retrofit project with the aim to reduce demand charges. To achieve this goal, this paper introduces an approach based on the analysis of all feasible energy consumption and peak reduction measures in an office building under different utility rate structure. The analysis includes all measures that are commonly adopted to decrease energy consumption and demand charges, specifically energy efficient measure and energy flexibility measures. The outcomes suggest the optimal combination that minimizes demand charges in commercial buildings.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16256/Zhang_Augenbroe_2018_Optimal Strategy for Demand Charge Reduction in an Office Building Under (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Huang, Sen</author><author>Chen, Yan</author><author>Ehrlich, Paul</author><author>Vrabie, Draguna</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>A Control-Oriented Building Envelope and Hvac System Simulation Model for a Typical Large Office Building</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>729-736</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>In this paper, we present a dynamic simulation model for a typical large ofﬁce building in the U.S., which can be used as a virtual testbed to enable advanced control research for heating, ventilation, and air conditioning (HVAC) systems. We employed EnergyPlus for calculating the building thermal load, and the Modelica Buildings library to model the dynamic behavior of the HVAC system. We used a functional mockup interface to enable run-time communication between the EnergyPlus model and the Modelica model. This simulation model can be driven by control inputs from the supervisory decision-making algorithms for advanced control system design and performance evaluation. To demonstrate the usage of the model, we performed the evaluation on two representative control sequences for large ofﬁce buildings with this model. Simulation data allows us to compare the energy performance of these two sequences and captures the evolution of the system dynamics at a high temporal granularity.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16257/Huang et al_2018_A Control-Oriented Building Envelope and Hvac System Simulation Model for a (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Powers, Aaron</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>A Pseudo-Transient Method for Modeling Flow Networks</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>737-742</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>A flow network is a modeling technique often used to model fluid flow in buildings and HVAC systems. This technique allows for fluid flows and pressures to be simulated without resorting to a full CFD analysis. A flow network is simulated by applying the steady-state conservation of mass principle at discrete points called nodes to create a system of nonlinear equations which can be solved by a variety of methods. Most solvers for building simulation flow networks are based on some derivative of Newton’s method. These solvers can show fast convergence when good initial guesses are provided but can be slow or divergent otherwise, especially in large networks. This paper introduces a new fictitious transient term to the nodal conservation of mass equations which allows for the equations to be decoupled and solved using explicit methods. This effectively removes the need for a multivariable nonlinear solver when simulating flow networks. The effects of a single model input parameter on stability and accuracy was investigated. Test cases were used to compare the new modeling technique to a traditional steady-state model using a Levenberg Marquardt solver. The results show that the new method creates almost no loss in accuracy while greatly improving the simulation time, especially for shorter time steps and larger models.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16258/Powers_2018_A Pseudo-Transient Method for Modeling Flow Networks (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Betz, Fred</author><author>Keck, Lyle</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>Challenges and Opportunities in Whole Building Water Modeling</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>743-750</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>Whole building water modeling continues to gain traction in the building industry with the public release of ASHRAE 191P Standard for the Efficient Use of Water in Building Mechanical Systems and LEED Pilot Credit: Whole Project Water Use Reduction. As this new field develops, technical challenges and opportunities arise that highlight the growing need for accurate whole building water modeling tools and procedures. This paper will explore the current challenges in defining plumbing fixture usage, irrigation calculations, and rainfall patterns as well as current methods and data sources for each section.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16259/Betz_Keck_2018_Challenges and Opportunities in Whole Building Water Modeling (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Aragon, Victoria</author><author>Quintero, Julian David</author><author>Gauthier, Stephanie</author><author>James, Patrick</author><author>Bahaj, Abubakr</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>Unpacking Mid-Season Heating Demand in Social Housing</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>752-757</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>The efficiency of residential heat supply systems is compromised when the heat load varies. Heat load variability is mainly rooted in space heating demand variations. Heating demand is expected to fluctuate the most during mid-season, as this is when users thermally adapt to warmer or colder weather, resulting in what is known as the “thermal adaptation lag”. The aim of this paper is to investigate this weather variability during mid-season leading to fluctuations of heating demand that impact the efficiency of heat supply systems. Here we present research conducted within five high-rise social housing tower blocks located in he city of Southampton,United Kingdom. Heating to the tower blocks is supplied through gas boilers to heat exchangers installed in each flat. Monthly heating demand monitoring from 2013 to 2017 at flat level shows that: (a) the variability of the heating demand is higher in the period November to March and is related to temperature variation, (b) the amount of heat required by Heating Degree Day is not constant. The analysis identifies potential implications for engineers designing heat supply systems for social housing which contribute to reducing the performance gap between building design and use.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16260/Aragon et al_2018_Unpacking Mid-Season Heating Demand in Social Housing (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Pillai, Jagan</author><author>Desai, Rushil</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>Dehumidification Strategies and Their Applicability Based on Climate and Building Typology</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>759-766</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>Dehumidification is a highly energy intensive process, especially in humid climates and for building typologies that require strict space humidity setpoints. Sub-cooling of air to condense out moisture using chilled water or refrigerant is the most common method for dehumidifying. Alternative strategies such as desiccant wheel, dual wheel and wrap around coils could more energy efficiently be used for certain climate zones and project types. Using energy models and results from a customized Excel-based tool, this paper evaluates applicability of each dehumidification strategy based on the local climate and building typology.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16261/Pillai_Desai_2018_Dehumidification Strategies and Their Applicability Based on Climate and (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Mohiuddin, Mohammed Salman</author><author>Zhao, Weihuan</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>Heat and Mass Transfer Analysis of the Micro-Porous Membrane/Phase Change Material Based Energy Recovery Ventilator</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>767-774</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>The work aims to investigate a unique membrane-based energy recovery ventilator (ERV) system combined with phase change material (PCM) to efficiently recover thermal energy and moisture between the incoming air and exhaust air from the buidling to reduce the HVAC system load. Heat and mass transfer simulations were conducted for this ERV system under various air temperatures and flow regimes. It has been found that the membrane/PCM based ERV system can achieve sensible effectiveness (heat recovery) of 65% - 98% while latent effectiveness (moisture recovery) of 60% - 80%.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16262/Mohiuddin_Zhao_2018_Heat and Mass Transfer Analysis of the Micro-Porous Membrane-Phase Change (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Protopapadaki, Christina</author><author>Saelens, Dirk</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>Sensitivity of Low-Voltage Grid Impact Indicators to Weather Conditions in Residential District Energy Modeling</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>783-790</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>Heat pumps and photovoltaic systems become more common in residential neighborhoods, where they alter the traditional relationship with the electricity distribution grid, causing congestion and voltage problems. This paper investigates the influence of weather data on low-voltage grid impact indicators calculated within a previously developed probabilistic framework. We compared results for seven different synthetic weather years, generated for Belgium using Meteonorm, ranging from “average” to “extreme cold winter and sunny summer”, as well as two future scenarios for 2050. Since peak demand and generation are influenced by ambient temperature and solar irradiation respectively, extreme values in weather inputs can potentially determine the outcome of an impact analysis. We, therefore, argue not to rely on average synthetic weather year profiles. Additionally, the impact of using a single representative week as alternative to year-long simulation was investigated.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16264/Protopapadaki_Saelens_2018_Sensitivity of Low-Voltage Grid Impact Indicators to Weather Conditions in (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Cruickshank, Robert F.</author><author>Florita, Anthony R.</author><author>Henze, Gregor P.</author><author>Corbin, Charles D.</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>Characterizing Electric Grid System Benefits of Mpc-Based Residential Load Shaping</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>791-798</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>Routinely encouraging and discouraging residential electric load throughout the day will be increasingly critical in efficiently managing the smart grid to reliably deliver clean, low-cost electricity. Yet, manipulating the duty cycles of thermostatically controlled loads such as heating, air conditioning, and hot water heaters can have the effect of destabilizing or stabilizing the grid. This work explores the potential for price-responsive control of residential air conditioning to shape electric demand at the distribution feeder level to minimize electricity production costs. Physical models of the interplay between building thermal and electric loads are used to simulate time-series temperature and load behaviour. Instantaneous load-adding and load-shedding opportunities are quantified in more than 100,000 individual homes on 204 distribution feeders with results presented for 35 cities across the United States. In the context of distributed model predictive control, simulation of feeder-level response to a residential day-ahead 5-minute pricing vector to 2,146 homes highlights an aggregate impact of flexible loads.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16265/Cruickshank et al_2018_Characterizing Electric Grid System Benefits of Mpc-Based Residential Load (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Jain, Achin</author><author>Nong, Derek</author><author>Nghiem, Truong X.</author><author>Mangharam, Rahul</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>Digital Twins for Efficient Modeling and Control of Buildings an Integrated Solution with Scada Systems</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>799-806</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>We develop an integrated solution for incorporating “digi- tal twins” of real buildings into existing SCADA systems, which enables real-time prediction and advanced control. These digital twins are either EnergyPlus (E+) or data- driven (D+) building models, whose input and output vari- ables are mapped to analogous real building OPC tags and track the real-time operation of the building. An E+ dig- ital twin can be used to provide predictions of the build- ing’s performance in different weather, usage, and energy pricing scenarios, which allows for accurate assessment of different control strategies. However, it is not suitable for optimization and predictive control due to its complexity. We develop scalable D+ digital twin based on Gaussian Processes (GP) for accurate prediction and advanced con- trol. A D+ digital twin is much easier, faster, and less ex- pensive to train than developing and tuning an E+ model, while still providing accurate power forecasts and being suitable for control. Data-driven Model Predictive Con- trol (MPC) optimizes control inputs of the predictive D+ model for energy curtailment with thermal comfort guar- antees in demand response applications. The MPC con- troller is integrated into the SCADA environment, demon- strating real-time in-the-loop control of D+ digital twins.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16266/Jain et al_2018_Digital Twins for Efficient Modeling and Control of Buildings an Integrated (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Park, June Young</author><author>Dougherty, Thomas</author><author>Nagy, Zoltan</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>A Bluetooth Based Occupancy Detection for Buildings</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>807-814</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>As occupants and their behaviors are responsible for a signiﬁcant share of the energy consumption in buildings, it is of important to gather occupancy data. In fact, gathering occupancy data is considered as one of the grand challenges in building information modeling. Capitalizing on the pervasiveness of mobile devices with Bluetooth (BT) functionality, in this paper, we propose an occupant detection system that uses the BT signal to infer occupant presence. We present the low-cost hardware based on the Raspberry Pi and the open-source software. We apply our approach in a real building environment with two experimental scenarios: 1) Occupancy estimation of a whole building level, and 2) Characterization of occupant types in a shared ofﬁce. We estimate the ratio r of detected BT devices to actual number of people to be r ≈ 0.64. Our results show robust detection of occupants, as well as successful characterization of occupancy types as stationary, regular occupants, and visitors. Our method can be deployed quickly, and does not require the occupants to install a speciﬁc software. Thus, the proposed approach is especially useful for retroﬁt solutions.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16267/Park et al_2018_A Bluetooth Based Occupancy Detection for Buildings (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>LeRiche, Elizabeth</author><author>McArthur, J. J.</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>A Test Cell to Infer Thermal Response of Building Components for Model Predictive Control Using Building Automation Sensors</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>815-822</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>The use of Model Predictive Controllers (MPC) in building HVAC systems has demonstrated significant energy savings. This approach relies on knowledge of occupancy, weather conditions, and building thermal dynamics to predict the future HVAC conditioning requirements. The thermal dynamics is usually modeled using a grey box model, which requires the knowledge of the buildings thermal mass, an unknown characteristic for many older buildings. This study analyzes the ability to determine thermal dynamic behavior without building construction knowledge. A test cell has been constructed to monitor typical building control points consisting of the ambient temperature, supply air conditions, occupancy, lighting, and plug loads along with outdoor air temperature and solar radiation. These are used in conjunction with surface temperature sensors to characterize their thermal response with the outdoor and indoor conditions. This paper presents the set-up of the test cell along with the preliminary study investigating the ability to solve for thermal mass using sensor measurements. The analysis conducted looks at the simplest thermal condition of the cell, the nighttime unoccupied condition, for the two most thermally slow elements, the concrete floor and ceiling slabs. The results from this preliminary analysis strongly indicate the potential to calculate thermal dynamic behavior using only BAS points. This will support the overall research goal of creating model predictive control approaches for existing building where exact thermal mass is unknown.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16268/LeRiche_McArthur_2018_A Test Cell to Infer Thermal Response of Building Components for Model (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Chen, Yan</author><author>Huang, Sen</author><author>Vrabie, Draguna</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>A Simulation Based Approach for Impact Assessment of Physical Faults: Large Commercial Building Hvac Case Study</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>823-830</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>We developed a simulation-based approach for fault impact analysis for a single duct variable air volume (VAV) system, and analyzed the dynamic and steady-state impact of equipment physical faults on building operation. The simulation model, a virtual testbed, can capture physical faults in the HVAC system of a large commercial building. The model can be used to generate data that can then be analyzed to quantify the impact of single or multiple faults. This paper illustrates the implementation of three physical faults: supply air temperature sensor bias, outdoor air temperature sensor bias, and cooling coil valve stuck. Each fault was simulated with several fault intensity levels and under different seasonal operating conditions. Then, we analyzed the impact of the above-mentioned faults using the energy and comfort metrics. The results show that the impact of a given physical fault depends on implemented control logic sequence and the seasonal operating conditions.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16269/Chen et al_2018_A Simulation Based Approach for Impact Assessment of Physical Faults (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Zhou, Hao</author><author>Huang, Yichun</author><author>Xue, Gavin</author><author>Chen, Chen</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>Development of an Empirical Method for Calculating Discharge Coefficients for Contam Models</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>298-303</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>Computational Fluid Dynamics (CFD) is a powerful and expensive technique to simulate natural ventilation. CONTAM, as an alternative computer program, is based on the bulk airflow network model therefore it is less computationally expensive. However, some key inputs, such as discharge coefficients, require user specifications.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16201/Zhou et al_2018_Development of an Empirical Method for Calculating Discharge Coefficients for (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Roth, Amir</author><author>Bull, Jamie</author><author>Criswell, Scott</author><author>Ellis, Peter</author><author>Glazer, Jason</author><author>Goldwasser, David</author><author>Kruis, Neal</author><author>Parker, Andrew</author><author>Philip, Santosh</author><author>Reddy, David</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>Scripting Frameworks for Enhancing Energyplus Modeling Productivity</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>312-319</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>Task automation is a great productivity enhancer in any workflow. In building energy modeling, scripting has emerged as a powerful tool for automating both standard tasks such as generating a code-minimum baseline model from a model of a proposed or actual building and for workflow customization. This paper presents four scripting frameworks for EnergyPlus. Eppy makes EnergyPlus input objects accessible as Python objects, allowing them to be manipulated programmatically. Modelkit is an embedded Ruby library that allows modelers to create parameterized templates that instantiate different specific EnergyPlus input files depending on parameter values. OpenStudio Measures provide programmatic access to the OpenStudio object model; that model is translated into an EnergyPlus input file. CBECC uses a custom scripting/rule engine that operates on the Standards Data Dictionary (SDD) building model schema; OpenStudio is used to translate SDD files to EnergyPlus input files. The paper discusses the philosophy behind each system, its architecture and core capabilities, and uses simple modeling tasks to show how each system is used in practice.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16202/Roth et al_2018_Scripting Frameworks for Enhancing Energyplus Modeling Productivity (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Nouidui, Thierry S.</author><author>Wetter, Michael</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>Simulatortofmu: A Python Utility to Support Building Simulation Tool Interoperability</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>325-330</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>The Functional Mock-up Interface (FMI) standard is an open standard for an application programming interface that allows run-time interoperability with other simulation tools, such as for co-simulation. As of today, more than 100 simulation tools use the FMI standard. However only few building simulation tools are exported as FMUs because of a lack of export utilities.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16204/Nouidui_Wetter_2018_Simulatortofmu (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Wilson, Eric</author><author>Merket, Noel</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>An Interactive Visualization Tool for Large-Scale Building Stock Modeling</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>338-345</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>Recent advancements in data science and high- performance computing are making it easier to run millions of building simulations, but meaningful visual- ization of such large datasets remains a challenge. This paper presents a new tool developed to view the results of large-scale OpenStudioOR&#xD;simulations of national, regional, or local building stocks. The tool processes millions of simulations to calculate measure savings, utility bills, carbon emissions, primary energy, and cost- effectiveness metrics at a high geographic resolution. Interactive visualizations of the building characteristics, consumption, and measure savings data include pro- portional symbol maps and histogram plots and can be filtered by any building characteristic.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16206/Wilson_Merket_2018_An Interactive Visualization Tool for Large-Scale Building Stock Modeling (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Kruis, Neal</author><author>Barnaby, Charles S.</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>Reading and Writing Standardized Hvac Performance Data: An Early Implementation of Ashrae Standard 205p</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>352-358</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>ASHRAE Standard 205P recently concluded its ﬁrst advisory public review. The standard, entitled “Standard Representation of Performance Simulation Data for HVAC&amp;R and Other Facility Equipment”, makes the ﬁrst attempt to standardize the way performance data is conveyed between HVAC equipment manufacturers and energy modelers. The standard deﬁnes speciﬁc data elements that represent the complete performance of equipment for use in building performance simulation tools.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16208/Kruis_Barnaby_2018_Reading and Writing Standardized Hvac Performance Data (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Corney, Andrew</author><author>Bajic, Vladimir</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild co-organized by ASHRAE and IBPSA-USA Chicago, IL September 26-28, 2018</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>359-366</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>ASHRAE 55 is a standard that provides a way for occupant thermal comfort to be measured for building designs. It goes beyond air temperature to account for a range of factors, so that a more holistic assessment of occupant thermal satisfaction can be measured.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16209/Corney_Bajic_2018_2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild co-organized by (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Truesdell, Kerger</author><author>Corney, Andrew</author><author>Bajic, Vladimir</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>A Detailed Methodology for Cloud-Based Daylight Analysis</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>367-373</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>It is often difficult for practitioners to trust analysis software if its methods are not transparent and welldocumented. The purpose of this paper is to open for review, comment and reference the methodology used within Sefaira to help those who use it and those who field requests to respond to its outputs.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16210/Truesdell et al_2018_A Detailed Methodology for Cloud-Based Daylight Analysis (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Lee, JeeEun</author><author>Peng, Mingbo</author><author>Kwan, Shin-yi</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>Integration of Environmental Simulation to Parametric Design Workflow: Thermal Comfort and Daylight</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>374-381</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>This paper suggests a parametric design workflow of an institution building in New Orleans, Louisiana based on parametric, climate-based analysis. This workflow is aimed to support the early design process with passive strategies to enhance occupant thermal comfort and daylight conditions of the building as well as its energyefficiency. By analyzing the hot and humid climate of New Orleans and the needs of muliple spatial programs, including open spaces, workplaces, and residential units, parametric models were generated to simulate the annual thermal comfort and daylight conditions, which provides grounds for comparison among parametric models. In response to the climate analysis and bioclimatic strategies, three design steps were implemented: self-shading, façade components, and multi-functional screens.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16211/Lee et al_2018_Integration of Environmental Simulation to Parametric Design Workflow (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Ghobad, Ladan</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>Daylighting and Energy Simulation Workflow in Performance- Based Building Simulation Tools</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>382-389</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>Accurate daylighting analysis for buildings has been developed along with energy simulation in performancebased analysis tools, such as: DesignBuilder, DIVA, Honeybee, and Insight360. However, users in professional practice do not have a complete understanding of the capabilities and limitations of these tools. Although these programs use the same (or equivalent) simulation engines, they could generate different results due to having different simulation workflows, default inputs, and user-defined inputs through the Graphic User Interface (GUI).</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16212/Ghobad_2018_Daylighting and Energy Simulation Workflow in Performance- Based Building (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Mirianhosseinabadi, Sedighehsadat</author><author>Mehta, Mohit</author><author>Bacchus, Jamy</author><author>Engineers, M. E.</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>Integrating Cfd with Bem in Early Design Stage to Optimize Design Solutions</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>390-397</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>Integrating Building Energy Modeling (BEM) and Computational Fluid Dynamic (CFD) early in the design process provides comprehensive information to design teams to select the optimum HVAC system in terms of thermal comfort. This paper is a review of previous CFD studies and also evaluates the thermal comfort inside a multipurpose arena bowl by using CFD analysis of the HVAC air-side system with different configurations using the IES Virtual Environment (IES VE) software. The challenges of this process and the software are addressed. Lastly, the integrated BEM is modified based on the optimized system solution and energy saving results over the baseline are presented.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16213/Mirianhosseinabadi et al_2018_Integrating Cfd with Bem in Early Design Stage to Optimize Design Solutions (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Čekon, Miroslav</author><author>Plášek, Josef</author><author>Slávik, Richard</author><author>Fečer, Tomáš</author><author>Juráś, Peter</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>An Experimental and Numerical Model of a Solar Facade Prototype with Transparent Insulation and Selective Absorber</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>398-405</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>The presented study focuses on the modelling of a Transparent Insulation Material (TIM) incorporated in a façade structure. An experimental prototype of a Transparent Insulation Façade (TIF) with and without a selective absorber was developed as part of the opaque building envelope. Experimental measurements were performed using a climatic chamber test with the aim of verifying theoretical models. A detailed comparative investigation of the thermal performance of both TIFs was conducted using numerical CFD methods. The proper consistency between the simulation results and the experimental data indicated that the simulation model was reliable for predicting the overall thermal performance of TIM based solar façade prototypes.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16214/Čekon et al_2018_An Experimental and Numerical Model of a Solar Facade Prototype with (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Mottaghi, Seyed Arman</author><author>Mora, Rodrigo</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>Model-Based Coupling of Air and Hydronic Systems Operation in a Typical Classroom of a High-Performance Academic Building</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>406-413</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>A High-Performance Academic Building (HPAB) was studied following the evidence from design documents, an energy model, and operational data suggesting that the building’s performance is not entirely reflecting the design intent. Several operational anomalies were detected, including the operation of the mechanical system on the demand side, where an air system and a radiant system work in parallel.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16215/Mottaghi_Mora_2018_Model-Based Coupling of Air and Hydronic Systems Operation in a Typical (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Goldwasser, David</author><author>Ball, Brian</author><author>Farthing, Amanda</author><author>Frank, Stephen</author><author>Im, Piljae</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>Advances in Calibration of Building Energy Models to Time Series Data</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>422-429</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>Advanced building analytics and control applications, such as fault detection and diagnostics and model predictive control, benefit from building energy models calibrated to time series data. This paper recommends best practices for aligning EnergyPlus™ model time series output with measured building performance. These include the use of subcalibration procedures to fine-tune envelope, heat transfer, and mechanical system parameters; initialization of zone temperatures to match observed conditions at the beginning of each calibration period; and calculation of calibration metrics across multiple run periods using a new OpenStudio reporting measure.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16217/Goldwasser et al_2018_Advances in Calibration of Building Energy Models to Time Series Data (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Riet, Freek Van</author><author>Wolf, Ruben De</author><author>Verhaert, Ivan</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>Experimental Calibration of a One-Dimensional Model for Simulating the Dynamic Thermal Behaviour of Stratified Lakes</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>430-437</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>With increasing insulation, cooling in buildings gains importance regarding overall primary energy consumption. By integrating lakes in cooling systems, this consumption can be reduced. To optimally design these systems, it is beneficial to have insight in the dynamic thermal behaviour of the lake and its interaction with the cooling system. As simulations can provide such insight, a onedimensional lake model is calibrated and validated in this paper. In order to do so, first the lake’s depth was mapped in preliminary measurements. After that, temperature and light intensity at its center were measured at 15 different depths for 11 months. Weather conditions were logged in detail by a national weather station nearby the lake. The preliminary measurements showed that the lake had a maximum depth of 7.8m, a surface area of 16000m2 and a total volume of 100000m3. The data of the light intensity showed a time-dependency throughout the year. The calibrated model estimates most data with an error of only ±2ڮC. Therefore, it can be used to analyse the potential of the lake for cooling purposes.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16218/Riet et al_2018_Experimental Calibration of a One-Dimensional Model for Simulating the Dynamic (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Fu, Yangyang</author><author>Wetter, Michael</author><author>Zuo, Wangda</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>Modelica models for data center cooling systems</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>438-445</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>This paper presents a package of Modelica models, which are dedicated to data center cooling systems and recently added to the Modelica Buildings library. To demonstrate the usage of this package, we modeled a chilled water system with an integrated wateside economizer, and an air-cooled direct expansion system with an airside economizer. These models are then applied to evaluate the control performance. After that we performed a detailed comparison in terms of systemlevel energy efficiency, economizing hours and supply air conditions for the two cooling systems. The advantages and disadvantages of this package are finally summarized and discussed.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16219/Fu et al_2018_Modelica models for data center cooling systems (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Yoon, Yeo Beom</author><author>Mirianhosseinabadi, Sedighehsadat</author><author>Song, Suwon</author><author>Cho, Soolyeon</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>Calibrated Simulation Modeling for Performance Analysis in Bcvtb Platform</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>446-453</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>Building Automation System is used for operation, management, and control of building systems. Energy simulation modeling can be used as a tool to analyze the performance of buildings. This paper discusses how the Building Controls Virtual Test Bed (BCVTB) program can be used as a platform to link multiple programs and systems to generate and analyze the advanced building performance data. A real-time process of building commissioning and performance analysis, utilizing the BCVTB platform, is tested. Results are discussed in terms of pros and cons of this approach. Future development plans are proposed to improve the energy performance of buildings.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16220/Yoon et al_2018_Calibrated Simulation Modeling for Performance Analysis in Bcvtb Platform (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Iqbal, Javed</author><author>Dirkes II, James V.</author><author>Andras, Reith</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>Implications of Epbd Compliant Facade on Primary Cooling Energy Demand in Central Europe: Theory Vs. Practice</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>454-461</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>The buildings sector is responsible for 40% of energy consumption and 36% of the CO2 emissions in the European Union [1].The non-residential building sector makes 25% of the total EU building stock which is more challenging to evaluate due to mixed building types (offices, hospitals etc.) and respective usage pattern. Due to recent rapid development in the commercial sector, the electricity consumption has increased in an average by more than 70% primarily due to high plug loads, hence increasing the cooling energy demand. In line with the key EU directives targeting CO2 emission reduction, current regulations have stringent insulation requirements for the building envelope. The current study focuses on evaluating the effect of the regulations on high internal load (plug loads, occupancy etc.) buildings in central Europe. The annual primary heating and cooling energy demands have been calculated by dynamic thermal simulation software for standard and future IPCC (2030) A1B climatic scenarios for three buildings in Budapest, Hungary that meet EU’s directives, the Energy Performance of Buildings Directive (EPBD). The results show that by implementing the current local regulations (TNM recast) with more stringent requirements than the previous code (7/2006 TNM) leads to increased primary cooling energy up to 10% in all the simulated cases. This increase is even more profound with IPCC (2030) A1B weather scenario. With increasing thermal insulation due to the current regulatory framework, the consequences can be adverse on overall primary energy consumption and appear to conflict with future EU’s low-energy, net zero energy and CO2 emission reduction goals.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16221/Iqbal et al_2018_Implications of Epbd Compliant Facade on Primary Cooling Energy Demand in (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Desai, Arjun</author><author>Vaidya, Prasad</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>Quantifying the Reduction in Cooling Energy Due to Passive Cooling Techniques for Indian Cities</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>462-469</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>Past studies have quantified the potential of various passive design strategies to achieve thermal autonomy. Bhadra, Vaidya, &amp; Sarraf (2017) have shown that for 60 cities in India, minimum thermal autonomy calculated by using the thermostat set point as the benchmark, is at 12% for night cooling, 75% for evaporative cooling, 28% for ground cooling and 32% for radiant cooling. This paper takes that approach further and quantifies the reduction in cooling energy due to three passive strategies, using the CIBSE method with Cooling Degree Days (CDD) for 60 Indian cities.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16222/Desai_Vaidya_2018_Quantifying the Reduction in Cooling Energy Due to Passive Cooling Techniques (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Jradi, Muhyiddine</author><author>Veje, Christian T.</author><author>Jørgensen, Bo Nørregaard</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>Deep Energy Retrofit Vs Improving Building Intelligence – Danish Case Study</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>470-477</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>This study provides a preliminary assessment of the trade-off between deep energy retrofit and improving the building intelligence within an energy renovation process. A standard Danish office building from the 1980’s is considered as a case study. A detailed energy model was developed in EnergyPlus to simulate the dynamic performance of the case study building. Various deep energy retrofit measures were implemented and assessed. In addition, different measures to improve the energy efficiency and intelligence of the building were investigated and simulated with emphasis on European Standard EN 15232 recommendations for control and management of heating, ventilation and lighting systems.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16223/Jradi et al_2018_Deep Energy Retrofit Vs Improving Building Intelligence – Danish Case Study (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Jradi, Muhyiddine</author><author>Veje, Christian T.</author><author>Jørgensen, Bo Nørregaard</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>Technical and Economic Assessment of a Danish Public School Energy Renovation Using Dynamic Energy Performance Model</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>478-485</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>This study targets the public schools sector in Denmark, considering a case study of an 11,900 m2 School in Odense, and reporting the overall process of energy modeling, performance simulation and assessment of renovation measures. A holistic model was developed and calibrated using measured energy data. Various energy renovation measures and packages were investigated employing a holistic approach and considering the technical, economic and environmental impacts. A deep energy renovation package was recommended lifting the school energy rating to comply with the BR15 Danish building regulations, reducing energy consumption by 54.2% with an annual primary energy consumption of 65.5 kWh/m2.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16224/Jradi et al_2018_Technical and Economic Assessment of a Danish Public School Energy Renovation (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Yu, Cong</author><author>Pan, Wei</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>Effects of Shading on the Energy Consumption of High-Rise Office Buildings in Hong Kong</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>486-493</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>This paper aims to investigate the effects of shading from the building itself and nearby buildings on the energy consumption of high-rise office buildings in Hong Kong. The paper first analyzes the typical shading effects on energy use in Hong Kong by investigating four typical office buildings with different building typologies and surroundings. The paper then chooses one typical building for further parametric study. Energy consumption regression models are established under different height, building interval and orientation conditions. The findings reveal that the shading effects show a great influence on energy consumption of highrise buildings and cannot be neglected.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16225/Yu_Pan_2018_Effects of Shading on the Energy Consumption of High-Rise Office Buildings in (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Eslamirad, Nasim</author><author>Mahdavinejad, Mohamadjavad</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>External Shadings Effect on Operating Energy Based on Lcea, Case Study: A Residential Building in Tehran</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>494-501</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>Increasing awareness of energy waste and destructive environmental effects of buildings has led to particular tendencies toward improving buildings details and performance in order to save energy resources and protect the environment. The daylightophil envelope protects the building from sunlight by preventing the solar radiation entrancement, then causes decreasing building loads in the operational phase. At the essence, this paper focuses on building Operational Energy (OE) and Embodied Energy (EE), when external shading systems are applied as an energy efficient element in the building. To evaluate external shading system role in building thermal needs and environmental impact, Life Cycle Energy Assessment (LCEA) method is employed. LCEA is influenced by OE and EE. EE is total energy consumed in the life cycle stages of building, whereas operational energy is the energy required to operate the building in the process such as space conditioning, lighting and operating other building appliances. LCEA notion not only illustrates the usefulness of the building's life cycle but also facilitates decision-making on the energy efficiency of the system to benefit the optimization. The comparison baseline for simulation is the shading sytems effect on the consumued energy by building in Tehran. The results prove that building in the target climate with an external shading meets the lower OE over the building life cycle about 4%, and accordingly lower-polluting because of the lower consumed energy – especially cooling loads –comparison with the absence of shading system, but the shading material causes some environmental impact too.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16226/Eslamirad_Mahdavinejad_2018_External Shadings Effect on Operating Energy Based on Lcea, Case Study (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Zhou, Hao</author><author>Xiong, Chenguang</author><author>Huang, Yichun</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>Performance Evaluation and Optimization of Ventilated Double Skin Facade in China</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>502-509</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>Double-skin facades (DSF) are gaining prevalence in China. However, the benefits of DSF have not been realized due to the lack of quantitative design verification before construction, and operational challenges. Some building owners have even chosen not to turn on mechanically ventilated DSF. This paper presents a design and operation analysis of the inactive DSF in an office building in China. Its performance was carefully studied with Computational Fluid Dynamics (CFD) and Dynamic Thermal Simulation (DTS). An optimized ventilation rate and annual operation schedule are proposed and the investigation approach is introduced.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16227/Zhou et al_2018_Performance Evaluation and Optimization of Ventilated Double Skin Facade in (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Bhatnagar, Mayank</author><author>Mathur, Jyotirmay</author><author>Garg, Vishal</author><author>Iqbal, Javed</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>Development of a Method for Selection of Representative City in a Climate Zone</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>510-517</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>A building is a boundary between an outdoor climate and indoor conditions. The building energy consumption, notably the energy used for air-conditioning is closely related to outdoor climate. The Solar Radiation, Drybulb Temperature and Relative Humidity are the important climatic parameters which affect building’s thermal and visual conditions. The energy codes development analyses and evaluation of new technologies with respect to energy savings and financial viability have been carried out for selected cities that are supposed to represent any particular climate zone. There is a significant change in thermal loads in different cities of a climate zone. Selection of a representative city for a climatic zone is important because it needs to reflect average climatic conditions for a particular climate zone accurately. This study presents a new method that has been developed for the selection of a representative city in any climate zone, using the principle of Euclidean distance approach having a dry-bulb temperature, wet bulb temperature and solar radiation as three axes. The city having minimum Euclidean distance with respect to remaining cities of the same climatic zone is proposed to be taken as a representative city. The proposed method has been applied on each of the five existing climatic zones of India according to National Building Code (NBC) of India and eight climate zones according to ASHRAE Standard 169-2013. The results show representative city according to NBC climate zone classification: Ahmedabad (hot and dry), Lucknow (composite), Kolkata (warm and humid), Bengaluru (temperate) and Srinagar (cold); and according to ASHRAE Standard 169-2013: Ratnagiri (0 A), Ahmedabad (0 B), Kolkata (1 A), Varanasi (1 B), Tezpur (2 A), Amritsar (2 B), Shillong (3C) and Srinagar (4 B).</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16228/Bhatnagar et al_2018_Development of a Method for Selection of Representative City in a Climate Zone (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>McDowell, Timothy P.</author><author>Letellier-Duchesne, Samuel</author><author>Kummert, Michaël</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>A New Method for Determining Sub-Hourly Solar Radiation from Hourly Data</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>518-525</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>Accurately computing the solar irradiance in building performance software (BSP) is necessary to reliably predict the thermal behavior of many building related processes as well as the performance of renewable energy generators. While most of the simulations are performed at higher resolutions, up to 1-minute, the solar radiation data is often provided with weather data files at an hourly time scale. This work investigates the way popular building simulation programs interpolate the hourly solar radiation data and proposes a new algorithm that fixes deficiencies of other common methods. Program algorithms are identified and described and compared against high resolution measured irradiation data for three stations in the United States.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16229/McDowell et al_2018_A New Method for Determining Sub-Hourly Solar Radiation from Hourly Data (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Lin, Bo</author><author>Chen, Zhao</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>Energy Model Calibration for Campus Office Buildings</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>526-533</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>In order to achieve energy reduction, many buildings implement energy conservation measures (ECMs). Building energy model (BEM) is a useful tool for quantitative analysis of ECMs. However, uncalibrated model will generate misleading results. The BEM has to be calibrated to the as-operated condition based on metered data and building information. In this research, we applied variable selection method to prioritize calibration sequence and strategy. Critical variables that are significant to building energy use are identified through big data learning approaches. In the case study, we applied the methodology to campus office buildings in the U.S.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16230/Lin_Chen_2018_Energy Model Calibration for Campus Office Buildings (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Liu, Liu</author><author>Hao, Zhengwen</author><author>Niu, Fuxin</author><author>O'Neill, Zheng</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>Energy Modeling and Calibration of a Mixed-Use Building with Laboratories, Offices and Classrooms</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>534-541</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>In general, mixed-use buildings with laboratories, offices, and classrooms consume significant energy and are very energy intensive. These buildings provide great opportunities for energy efficiency improvement from mechanical and energy systems. However, the interconnected complexity of system and equipment in buildings with laboratories makes modeling of these buildings a unique and challenging task. This paper presents the development and calibration of a university mixed-used building using the EnergyPlus simulation program. The building under study is the South Engineering Research Center (SERC) building. Air Handler Units (AHU) equipped with Energy Recovery Units (ERU) supply 100% outside air to the laboratory spaces through terminal Variable Air Volume Boxes (VAV). Chilled water and hot water are delivered from the campus central energy plant. The modeling process, preliminary calibration, and verification results, as well as implementation issues encountered throughout the modeling and calibration processes from a user’s perspective, are presented and discussed.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16231/Liu et al_2018_Energy Modeling and Calibration of a Mixed-Use Building with Laboratories, (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Gucyeter, Basak</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>Calibration of a Building Energy Performance Simulation Model Via Monitoring Data</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>542-549</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>Energy performance gap is considered as one of the most significant issues associated with the assessment of energy consumption in the built environment. In order to narrow this gap, simulation approach for energy performance assessment are requires comprehensive calibration procedures. Calibrated energy performance models facilitate a baseline representation of existing building performance patterns, thus, further accuracy in diagnosis, operation and energy conservation measures (ECMs) become possible through the use of calibrated models. The present study presents an iterative approach for calibrating a building energy model using full year monitoring data. The methodology focuses on disclosing the steps in calibrating the simulation model and the relative sensitivities of the assumed and monitored parameters used in calibration. The magnitude of the alteration in different levels of calibrated simulation models are evaluated with Mean Bias Error (MBE) and Root Mean Square Error (RMSE) and the model accuracy is controlled through benchmarks defined by ASHRAE Guideline 14, International Performance Measurement and Verification Protocol (IPMVP) and Federal Energy Management Program (FEMP).</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16232/Gucyeter_2018_Calibration of a Building Energy Performance Simulation Model Via Monitoring (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Fu, Tat S.</author><author>Lyon, Edward G.</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>Building Energy Model Calibration: A Case Study Using Computational Fluid Dynamics with Air Leakage Testing and on- Site Weather Data</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>558-564</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>Whole building energy models of existing buildings are infrequently validated because of model complexity and the availability of reliable data. In this paper, the authors consider two important building energy simulation components – measured whole-building air leakage rates and on-site weather data — and study their effects on creating an accurate energy model of an existing office building in Massachusetts, USA using computational fluid dynamics (CFD) analysis. This case study shows that on-site weather data is critical in calibrating building energy models and that CFD analysis has a greater influence during a heating season compared to a cooling season in a cold climate.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16234/Fu_Lyon_2018_Building Energy Model Calibration (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Chen, Tony D.</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>A Quicker Method for Determining the Ua-Value of a Residential Building</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>565-572</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>The present study on determining the UA-value of a residential building is based on a simple heat-balance approach. It is quicker than any traditional long-term insitu measurement method. The supply and return air temperatures, the relative humidity of the heating and cooling system, and the outdoor ambient temperature were measured overnight, allowing the UA-value to be calculated from the system’s on and off time periods.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16235/Chen_2018_A Quicker Method for Determining the Ua-Value of a Residential Building (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Ye, Yunyang</author><author>Wang, Gang</author><author>Zuo, Wangda</author><author>Yang, Peilin</author><author>Keya, Joshi</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>Development of a Baseline Building Model of Auto Service and Repair Shop</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>573-580</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>To support the ASHRAE Building Energy Quotient (bEQ) standard, the ASHRAE Research 1771 is trying to identify baseline building energy models for major commercial buildings so that the modeled source EUI is close to the median source EUI of the same type of buildings in the 2003 CBECS data. This paper introduces the procedure of creating a baseline model for the auto service and repair shops as they account for 2% quantity, 0.3% total floor area, and 0.2% energy consumption among the commercial buildings. First, we introduced a method to create the geometry model using the data collected from the 2003 CBECS data, reports, and existing building samples. Then a systematic approach is developed to identify the model inputs unrelated to geometry. Ultimately, the baseline model of auto service and repair shop is validated by using the median source EUI from the 2003 CBECS data. The results indicate that the relative errors between the source EUI of the new model and the median EUI from the 2003 CBECS data is 12.33%.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16236/Ye et al_2018_Development of a Baseline Building Model of Auto Service and Repair Shop (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Baker, Kristopher S.</author><author>Jia, Xun</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>Modeling Mission Critical Facilities for Leed: Lessons Learned</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>581-587</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>The critical facility market has grown exponentially in recent years with numerous new data centers being built worldwide. With its unique characteristics, special attention needs to be paid when modeling the performance of the data centers for design or Leadership in Energy and Environmental Design certification (LEED). This paper presents a technical overview of data centers, including a few components and unique characteristics; a description of various configurations such as hot aisle/cold aisle containment, economizing and virtualization; and an overview of the LEED modeling requirement for data center applications. It also provides techniques on properly simulating the energy use of data centers for design or LEED purpose.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16237/Baker_Jia_2018_Modeling Mission Critical Facilities for Leed (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Desai, Rushil</author><author>Shah, Shivani</author><author>Nagpal, Shreshth</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>Investigating the Impact of Cost-Based and Carbon-Based Renewable Energy Generation and Storage Sizing Strategies on Carbon Emissions for All-Electric Buildings</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>588-593</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>Current renewable energy system, and storage, sizing and optimization designs typically focus on technoeconomic modeling. This paper proposes sizing and optimization based on greenhouse gas emissions as a metric as opposed to energy costs, as a method more in line with the intent of installing grid-integrated clean energy systems. Using a combination of simple energy models and results derived from a spreadsheet based tool, the authors discuss the benefits and limitations of both approaches, and the applicability of each in present as well as future scenarios.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16238/Desai et al_2018_Investigating the Impact of Cost-Based and Carbon-Based Renewable Energy (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Kim, Ok</author><author>Knudsen, Michael Dahl</author><author>Petersen, Steffen</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>Peak Load Reduction of District Heating by Control of Indoor Public Swimming Pool</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>594-599</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>In Denmark, the first district heating (DH) plant was built in 1903 and today about 64% of all residential buildings are connected to DH. The demand for DH is steadily increasing in and around major cities as more buildings are built for the increasing population. As a result, larger peak demands occur that might exceed the current DH production and/or distribution capacities. To avoid or minimise this, existing thermal capacities in the city could be utilized to shift loads from peak to nonpeak periods and hence reduce or avoid the rather large public infrastructure investments needed to expand the existing DH capacities. Such existing capacities could be for example design containers, swimming pools, underground aquifers, soils, and lakes.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16239/Kim et al_2018_Peak Load Reduction of District Heating by Control of Indoor Public Swimming (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Jose, Ivan</author><author>Traube, Caroline</author><author>Spies, Skander</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>Refining Energy Model Data to Develop a Narrative: Guidelines for Effective Visual Communication</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>600-606</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>Building simulations contain incredibly large amounts of information. Actionable data is often overwhelmed by the sheer quantity and cryptic nature of energy model inputs and outputs. The true value of modeling analysis often depends on effectively communicating the relevant information to decision makers in a timely fashion. Often, modelers have compelling data to share and a rough storyboard for decision makers, but let extraneous data or ineffective communication confuse the issues. This paper shows how concepts from the field of informational graphics including effective data visualization can successfully be adapted to building performance modeling to ensure the stories that modelers want to tell shine through. If done successfully, the value of building energy modeling is enhanced throughout the design and operations process.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16240/Jose et al_2018_Refining Energy Model Data to Develop a Narrative (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Hou, Gaoyang</author><author>Taherian, Hessam</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>Ground Source Heat Pump with Horizontal Ground Buried Pipes: Modelling and Optimization with Trnsys</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>607-614</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>The energy consumption of HVAC systems in both residential and industrial buildings is always an important problem. Geothermal sources are becoming one of the most attracting source for building HVAC systems. However, geothermal system operation involves varied conditions, various heat pump parameters, dynamic building loads and different ground loop parameters. Inaccurate design of each component leads to a significant departure from efficient performance which results in high energy use. Objective of this work is to simulate and optimize a geothermal HVAC system with TRNSYS. A control strategy is used to the simulation to find out best parameters combination of heat pump, horizontal ground buried pipes, and the liquid to air heat exchanger. The system has been modeled in Birmingham, Alabama. The results show that there is delicate balance that has to be maintained between the fluid temperature exiting the ground loop and the amount of heat delivered by the heat pump to the house. As a result, the control system parameters are highly important.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16241/Hou_Taherian_2018_Ground Source Heat Pump with Horizontal Ground Buried Pipes (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Miao, Rui</author><author>Yu, Yao</author><author>Audette, Rick</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>Investigation and Evaluation of a Horizontally Bored Geothermal Heat Pump System Used in the Cold Climate of the U.s.</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>615-622</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>Geothermal Heat Pump (GHP) systems equipped with horizontally bored underground pipes are a variant of a conventional horizontal closed-loop GHP system. The development of this type of system benefits from a horizontal drilling technique that allows the installation of horizontal heat exchangers in the deeper ground at different layers. Like a vertical closed-loop system, the horizontal boreholes are typically grouted in order to enhance the heat transfer performance. This type of system is less disturbed by outdoor weather compared to conventional horizontal closed-loop systems and thus may have higher cooling and heating capacities for larger building applications. Although horizontally bored GHP systems have their own advantages, this type system is not as widely used as conventional vertical or horizontal closed-loop systems, especially in cold-climate regions of the U.S. This paper aims to investigate and evaluate a horizontally bored underground GHP system currently used in an airport terminal located in Grand Forks in North Dakota (Climate Zone 7). This study includes a detailed description regarding this airport facility and an in-depth building energy simulation performed by using the commercial energy simulation software packages, Trane Trace 700 and GLHEPro 5.0. The models used in the simulation have been calibrated by using actual utility bills. The results indicate that the potential energy savings of this building are 17% compared to a conventional HVAC system. However, the corresponding energy cost savings are -7%, due to the extremely low natural gas price in this cold-climate region compared to electricity.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16242/Miao et al_2018_Investigation and Evaluation of a Horizontally Bored Geothermal Heat Pump (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Gautam, Khem Raj</author><author>Andresen, Grom Bruun</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>Performance of Heat Pump Assisted Building-Integrated Combined Photovoltaic Thermal Solar Collectors (bipvt) in Cold Climate</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>623-630</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>This paper evaluates configurations of indirect solar assisted heat pump systems with building-integrated combined&#xD;photovoltaic thermal solar collectors (BiPVT) in cold climates. Energy simulations of these systems show that the system coefficient of performance (COP) can&#xD;reach up to 5.6 for some selected configurations. Other configurations can provide a high solar fraction and a better&#xD;collector efficiency (up to 43%) at the expense of lower COP. A high COP and a better collector efficiency do not necessarily&#xD;translate into a better investment because, factors like buying and selling prices of the heat and the electricity equally important. The economic performance of different configurations in a dynamic multi-dimensional comparison suggests that the relatively simple system without a heat pump can be a better overall choice for the&#xD;cold climates.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16243/Gautam_Andresen_2018_Performance of Heat Pump Assisted Building-Integrated Combined Photovoltaic (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Ganji, Hoda Barzegar</author><author>Utzinger, Dennis Michael</author><author>Renken, Kevin J.</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>An Analysis on the Thermal Performance of a Horizontal Earth Tube System</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>631-638</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>The Aldo Leopold Foundation (ALF) located near Baraboo, WI, employs several passive approaches including using a Horizontal Earth Tube System (HETS). The simulation during the design level indicated that HETS would perform better than an enthalpy-heat-recovery system precooling and dehumidifying the air, but not quite as well preheating the air in winter. The earth tube model which was used in the design simulation had not been validated. This paper focuses on setting up a data collection system to measure the amount of precooling. A bulk flow model and a CFD1 model are further developed based on the collected data.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16244/Ganji et al_2018_An Analysis on the Thermal Performance of a Horizontal Earth Tube System (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Azizkhani, Mehdi</author><author>Baltazar, Juan-Carlos</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>Integrating Modeling and Simulation Tools with Learnings from Nature: A Methodology for Form Generation by Emulating the Constructal Law of Nature</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>639-645</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>The purpose of this paper is to illustrate a methodology for integrating the learnings from nature with modeling and simulation tools for form configuration of building components in the early phases of design. Although the form configurations of living organisms may look random at first sight, the “constructal law” of nature governs these configurations for a continuously optimized performance such as in the case of the branching patterns of a tree. In this performance, the goal is to minimize the flow resistance subject to global fitness constraints of time, space, and weight. In this paper, first the principles of the constructal law have been qualitatively and quantitatively discussed. Second, following these principles and using Rhino/Grasshopper and the genetic algorithm, the form of a test case office plan as well as the configuration of its supply duct system have been optimized. Using Autodesk CFD, the air flow within the proposed duct system has been simulated, which shows a considerably better performance compared with the typical plenum duct system.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16245/Azizkhani_Baltazar_2018_Integrating Modeling and Simulation Tools with Learnings from Nature (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Shen, Xiaofei</author><author>Singhvi, Aman</author><author>Mengual, Andrea</author><author>Spastri, Maria</author><author>Watson, Victoria</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>Evaluating the Multi-Objective Optimization Methodology for Performance-Based Building Design in Professional Practice</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>646-653</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>This paper examines the applicability of a Multi Objective Optimization (MOO) methodology within a parametric design setup. The primary focus of MOO is to facilitate early stage decision making in professional High Performance Building (HPB) practice. With environmental variables and objectives stemming from all design disciplines, there is a need for designers and engineers to work together to capitalize on their varied expertise and achieve efficiencies in HPB design optimization. This paper outlines two experiments carried out using the Octopus plugin, which is a MOO solver, within the Grasshopper (GH) parametric design interface. The findings show promising outcomes, highlight potential opportunities, and identify limitations of the proposed methodology.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16246/Shen et al_2018_Evaluating the Multi-Objective Optimization Methodology for Performance-Based (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Maurer, Christoph</author><author>Wilson, Helen Rose</author><author>Curcija, Dragan C.</author><author>Kuhn, Tilmann E.</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>Using Digitalization for More Reliable and Less Expensive Building Performance Analysis</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>654-658</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>This paper analyses the current state of simulations and proposes ways to reduce the costs and to increase the reliability of building performance analysis. Functions in machine-code can be used to generate automatically simulation models for numerous simulation environments. Simulations models are proposed which adapt their accuracy and can therefore be used from very early up to late stages of the planning process. BIM based on semantic technologies can provide more flexibility and make it easier to find the right components. A semantic international product data base is planned to make it easier for practitioners to identify most suitable product.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16247/Maurer et al_2018_Using Digitalization for More Reliable and Less Expensive Building Performance (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Naboni, Emanuele</author><author>Silvia, Coccolo</author><author>Meloni, Marco</author><author>Scartezzini, Jean-Louis</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>Outdoor Comfort Simulation of Complex Architectural Designs a Review of Simulation Tools from the Designer Perspective</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>659-666</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>The expanding design interest in outdoor comfort design is today supported by a few software tools. Given their different user-friendliness, modelling environments and simulation engines, a rational inquiry is how they are integrated into the digital design flow of architects and urban planners, which may include complex forms developments. Preliminary work is conducted to select architect-friendly tools that support the analysis of urban microclimate. A minimum set of criteria (amongst them the use of 3D models, the capability of calculating Mean Radiant Temperature and visual graphical outputs) led to the pre-selection of CitySim Pro, ENVI-met, Autodesk Thermal CFD, Grasshopper plug-ins Honeybee / Ladybug.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16248/Naboni et al_2018_Outdoor Comfort Simulation of Complex Architectural Designs a Review of (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Delgoshaei, Parastoo</author><author>Heidarinejad, Mohammad</author><author>Austin, Mark A.</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>Combined Ontology-Driven and Machine Learning Approach to Monitoring of Building Energy Consumption</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>667-674</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>A number of studies within the building domain have independently considered knowledge representation and reasoning (KRR) and machine learning (ML). This paper explores opportunities for how these artiﬁcial intelligence (AI) technologies can be combined to provide synergic assistance in intelligent building systems. A case study is used to demonstrate the construction of semantic knowledge from weather and utility ontologies. That knowledge is used as a semantically annotated training set in clustering algorithms that identify consumption patterns, and the results of clustering are stored in ontologies for further inference. This paper presents a roadmap to intelligent building monitoring techniques that uses both historical data and the underlying semantic knowledge.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16249/Delgoshaei et al_2018_Combined Ontology-Driven and Machine Learning Approach to Monitoring of (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Zhang, Zhiang</author><author>Chong, Adrian</author><author>Pan, Yuqi</author><author>Zhang, Chenlu</author><author>Lu, Siliang</author><author>Lam, Khee Poh</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>A Deep Reinforcement Learning Approach to Using Whole Building Energy Model for Hvac Optimal Control</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>675-682</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>Whole building energy model (BEM) is difﬁcult to be used in the classical model-based optimal control (MOC) because of its high-dimension nature and intensive computational speed. This study proposes a novel deep reinforcement learning framework to use BEM for MOC of HVAC systems. A case study based on a real ofﬁce building in Pennsylvania is presented in this paper to demonstrate the workﬂow, including building modeling, model calibration and deep reinforcement learning training. The learned optimal control policy can potentially achieve 15% of heating energy saving by simply controlling the heating system supply water temperature.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Zotero</remote-database-name><language>en</language><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16250/Zhang et al_2018_A Deep Reinforcement Learning Approach to Using Whole Building Energy Model for (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>New, Joshua</author><author>Adams, Mark B.</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>Energyplus Performance Improvements Via Json Input Refactoring</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>320-324</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>EnergyPlus is the flagship whole-building energy simulation program developed by the U.S. Department of Energy. This paper describes the refactoring efforts around the EnergyPlus input processor to natively support JavaScript Object Notation (JSON), allow validation through use of a JSON schema validator, convert and validate typical EnergyPlus input data file (*.idf) files to JSON files, and improve related metrics such as: read time for schema and input files, parse time for processing input, and time to query/return data from EnergyPlus internal data structure. Performance improvements on sample files result in 14% and 60% reduction in schema and input file reads respectively, 36-62% reduction to process input, and 24-99+% query reduction for functions that take advantage of the new format. For the files tested, overall speedup realized as part of this JSON refactor is 1.6x to 5.4x.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16203/New_Adams_2018_Energyplus Performance Improvements Via Json Input Refactoring (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Chronis, Angelos</author><author>Stefopoulou, Foteini</author><author>Liapi, Katherine</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>Integration of Cfd Simulations in Compuational Design for Harnessing the Natural Ventilation Performance of Typical Atrium Spaces in Athens, Greece</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>331-337</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>This paper investigates the integratin of CFD in computational and parametric design and its potential in driving the optimization of the natural ventiatlion performance of buildings, using as a case study the courtyard spaces of the typical multistorey buidlings in the historic center of Athens, Greece. The study employs a multi-scalar simulation approach and shape optimization techniques to asses the poential of using CFD to drive the design of retrofitted membranes that enhance the natural ventilation of the unused courtyards.&#xD;By parametrically modeling a membrane component on a representative courtyard case and using a Genetic Algorithm (GA) optimization along with a Fast Fluid dynamics (FFD) CFD solver that allows for fast iterative CFD simulations, the study aims to produce localized retrofitting interventions to increase the air quality of the courtyards and the ventilation performance of the buildings.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Google Scholar</remote-database-name><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16205/Chronis et al_2018_Integration of Cfd Simulations in Compuational Design for Harnessing the (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Sanchez, Charles S.</author><author>Xiaoquin, Zhang</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>Visualization of CFD Simulation Results in VR Environment for Design Feedback</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>346-351</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>In the tropics, where air-conditioning consumes around 50% of the electricity, natural ventilation is a primary passive design strategy. Due the complexity of natural wind flow, Computational Fluid Dynamics (CFD) simulations are used to evaluate the efficiency of applied natural ventilation, however, architects and designers find it difficult to visualize the results provided by these simulations, something that can be improved with the&#xD;use of better visualization tools. This research project uses a BIM created unit as a case study for CFD simulation of natural ventilation displayed in a VR environment, in order to improve design feedback and&#xD;the visualization of simulation data for natural ventilation.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16207/Sanchez_Xiaoquin_2018_Visualization of CFD Simulation Results in VR Environment for Design Feedback (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Zakrzewski, Thomas</author><author>Stephens, Brent</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>Building Integrated Cogeneration System Design Sizing and Analysis for Climate Disruption</title><secondary-title>BUILDING INTEGRATED COGENERATION SYSTEM DESIGN SIZING AND ANALYSIS FOR CLIMATE DISRUPTION</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>414-421</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>Normalized historical weather files are often utilized in whole-building energy simulations to quantitatively determine performance. Predictive building thermal and energy demand response to climate disruption can be evaluated through statistical and hourly simulation-based procedures. The WeatherShift™ application provides an opportunity to dynamically investigate design sizing sensitivity and operation of building integrated cogeneration systems (BICS) to climate disruption scenarios using industry standard reference EnergyPlus Weather (EPW) weather files. In order to determine the impact of future climate change earlier in the integrated design processes as it relates to building integrated cogeneration system performance and design sizing, hourly energy and loads simulation analysis was carried out using a reference commercial prototype building with projected future global climate weather models for two representative concentration pathways for Climate Zone 5A, Chicago. The ASHRAE 90.1-2013 reference building model was iteratively simulated in EnergyPlus simulation program with associated EnergyPlus Weather (EPW) TMY3 weather file and then “shifted” for 2026-2045 future years using WeatherShift™ to produce hourly time-step thermal and electrical load profiles. The ability to test cogeneration resiliency from definitive climate science and projections provides a value proposition for building owners and operators in terms of climate preparedness and adaptation considerations. Specific to the distribution climate model projections and emissions scenario considered, the experimental simulated results indicate that an optimally sized cogeneration system can maintain total fuel and energy cost, source energy, and greenhouse gas emissions savings relative to an ASHRAE 90.1-2013 minimally energy compliant reference building models.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><remote-database-name>Google Scholar</remote-database-name><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16216/Zakrzewski_Stephens_2018_Building Integrated Cogeneration System Design Sizing and Analysis for Climate (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Shazilza</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>Energy Modeling of Multi-Storied Residential Buildings – a Manual Calibration Approach</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title></titles><periodical><full-title>SimBuild 2018</full-title></periodical><pages>550-557</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>In this paper evidence based manual calibration approach is adopted to calibrate five mixed-mode multi-storied apartment blocks in composite climate of India. The baseline models are calibrated using monthly energy-use curve and validated using statistical indices. It is inferred that the evidence based manual calibration technique has fairly validated the energy-use profile of the chosen case studies and are found to be within acceptable tolerances (i.e. ±25% for percentage error, ±15% (CV (RMSE) and ±5% for MBE%).</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: SimBuild 2018</research-notes><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16233/Shazilza_2018_Energy Modeling of Multi-Storied Residential Buildings – a Manual Calibration (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>SimBuild 2018</custom3></record><record><database name="MyLibrary">MyLibrary</database><source-app name="Zotero">Zotero</source-app><ref-type name="Conference Proceedings">10</ref-type><contributors><authors><author>Wetter, Michael</author><author>Hu, Jianjun</author><author>Grahovac, Milica</author><author>Eubanks, Brent</author><author>Haves, Philip</author></authors></contributors><titles><title>OpenBuildingControl: Modeling feedback control as a step towards formal design, specification, deployment and verification of building control sequences</title><secondary-title>2018 Building Performance Analysis Conference and SimBuild</secondary-title><short-title>OpenBuildingControl</short-title></titles><periodical><full-title>Proc. of Building Performance Modeling Conference and SimBuild</full-title></periodical><pages>775-782</pages><dates><year>2018</year><pub-dates><date>2018</date></pub-dates></dates><publisher>IBPSA-USA</publisher><abstract>This paper presents ongoing work to develop tools and a process that will allow building designers to instantiate control sequences, configure them for their project, assess their performance in closed loop building energy simulation, and then export these sequences (i) for the control provider to bid on the project and to implement the sequences through machine-to-machine translation, and (ii) for the commissioning agent to verify their correct implementation.&#xD;The paper reports on the following: (i) The specification of a Control Description Language, (ii) its use to implement a subset of the ASHRAE Guideline 36 sequences, released as part of the Modelica Buildings library, (iii) its use in annual closed-loop simulations of a variable air-volume flow system, and (iv) lessons learned regarding simulation of closed loop control.&#xD;In our case study, the Guideline 36 sequences yield 30% lower annual site HVAC energy use, under comparable comfort, than sequences published earlier by ASHRAE. The 30% differences in annual HVAC energy consumption due to changes in the control sequences raises the question of whether the idealization of control sequences that is common practice in today's building energy simulation leads to trustworthy energy use predictions.</abstract><research-notes>The following values have no corresponding Zotero field:&#xD;periodical: Proc. of Building Performance Modeling Conference and SimBuild</research-notes><remote-database-name>Google Scholar</remote-database-name><urls><pdf-urls><url>internal-pdf://16263/Wetter et al_2018_OpenBuildingControl (Paper)2.pdf</url></pdf-urls></urls><custom1>Chicago, Illinois, USA</custom1><custom3>Proc. of Building Performance Modeling Conference and SimBuild</custom3></record></records></xml>